https://www.aminiaturemarvel.com/privacy-policy-update-2018-i-35.html?osCsid=9ualn65g57dgpe0fpu3o99uve4

Latest News
On Line shopping ProcessPostage & Packing InformationReturnsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy Update May 2018Cookie Policy
View/Hide
Store Categories
1:12 Scale Dolls House Accessories (482)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Bathroom (19)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Christmas (19)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Garden (7)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Glass (74)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Kitchen (87)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Miscellaneous (37)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Nursery (14)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Ornaments (25)
1:12 Scale Clarice Cliff Style (4)
1:12 Scale Staffordshire (3)
1:12 Scale Other Dollhouse Ornaments (18)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Packages (144)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Beverages (48)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Cleaning & Medical (35)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Food (52)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Knitting & Sewing (9)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Pets & Accessories (15)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Reading Material (26)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Books (5)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Comics (5)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Magazines (14)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Newspapers (2)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Rugs And Runner (4)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Toys, Games & Hobbies (11)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Clothing (11)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Dolls (0)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Exclusive Items (56)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Medical Centre (85)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Metal Minatures (94)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Office (10)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Pharmacy (143)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Pub (146)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Shop (312)
1:12 Scale Dolls House War Time Accessories (6)
1:24 Scale Dolls House Items (256)
1:24 Scale Figures (1)
1:24 Scale Food, Drinks and Cleaning Products (48)
1:24 Scale Furniture (0)1:24 Scale Glass (15)
1:24 Scale Kitchen Items (126)
1:24 Scale Miscellaneous Accessories (59)
1:24 Scale Ornaments (2)
1:24 Scale Wall Paper And Building Materials (5)
Dolls House DIY (186)
Dolls House Lighting & Electrical (5)
1:12 Scale Non Working Lights (5)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Candle Sticks & Candles (3)
1:12 Scale Oil Lamps (1)
1:12 Scale Table Lamps (1)
Dolls House Wood Turned Miniatures (3)
1:12 DIY Kits (1)
Jewellery Findings And Beads (279)
Jewellery Beads (79)
Crystal Bicone Beads (12)
Crystal Facet and Roundelle Beads (15)
Glass Beads (5)
Metal Beads (20)
Pearl Beads (3)
Other Beads (10)
Jewellery Filigrees (6)
Jewellery Findings (142)
Bead Caps (18)
Cameos & Rhinestones (8)
Clasps & Fittings (22)
Frames (2)
Miscellaneous Jewellery Components (61)
Settings (31)
Micro Jewellery Findings (52)
Sale Items (15)
You Are Here:
Home Privacy Policy Update May 2018
Privacy Policy Update May 2018
A Miniature Marvel
This Privacy Notice shall become effective as of 25 May 2018.
To see the Privacy Policy in effect up to that date, please click here.
This sets out the type of information we collect.  It tells you how the information is held and how it is used.  There are contact details for queries about your personal information.  All personal data collected will be treated in accordance with current data protection laws in the UK.
What information do we collect?
When you place an order online or by telephone, we create a record in your name containing your contact details.  For telephone orders we will also collect your credit/debit card details.  We do not retain card details once the payment has been processed.
We only hold basic personal information, e.g. contact details and we do not hold any sensitive personal data about members of the public.
The data controller for your personal data is Denise Johnson
How we use your information?
We use your personal information in the following ways:
To process orders placed online or by telephone.
To process payments.
What is the legal basis for processing your personal data?
Your personal data is processed solely for the purpose of processing sales orders.
We only circulate newsletters about our products, offers or holiday announcements and then only to those subscribers who have chosen to sign up to our news letter via our web page or have chosen to subscribe to news letter when you have created your account by selecting the subscribe box.
Who might we share this information with?
We do not share personal data with any other person or organisation.
Your rights and your personal data
You have the right to access personal data we hold on you.  You can request the personal data we hold.  You may also request that your personal data is deleted or corrected.  Once we have received your request we will respond within one month.
There are no fees or charges for the request.
Links to other sites
A Miniature Marvel may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites. Any information that is supplied on these sites will not be within our control and we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of these.
Contact details
Denise Johnson A Miniature Marvel
Hunters Ridge
Southfleet Avenue
New Barn
Longfield
Kent
DA3 7JQ
1:12 Scale Dolls House Accessories (482)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Bathroom (19)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Christmas (19)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Garden (7)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Glass (74)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Kitchen (87)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Miscellaneous (37)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Nursery (14)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Ornaments (25)
1:12 Scale Clarice Cliff Style (4)
1:12 Scale Staffordshire (3)
1:12 Scale Other Dollhouse Ornaments (18)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Packages (144)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Beverages (48)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Cleaning & Medical (35)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Food (52)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Knitting & Sewing (9)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Pets & Accessories (15)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Reading Material (26)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Books (5)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Comics (5)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Magazines (14)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Newspapers (2)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Rugs And Runner (4)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Toys, Games & Hobbies (11)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Clothing (11)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Dolls (0)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Exclusive Items (56)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Medical Centre (85)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Metal Minatures (94)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Office (10)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Pharmacy (143)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Pub (146)
1:12 Scale Dolls House Shop (312)
1:12 Scale Dolls House War Time Accessories (6)
1:24 Scale Dolls House Items (256)
1:24 Scale Figures (1)
1:24 Scale Food, Drinks and Cleaning Products (48)
1:24 Scale Furniture (0)1:24 Scale Glass (15)
1:24 Scale Kitchen Items (126)
1:24 Scale Miscellaneous Accessories (59)
1:24 Scale Ornaments (2)
1:24 Scale Wall Paper And Building Materials (5)
Dolls House DIY (186)
Dolls House Lighting & Electrical (5)
1:12 Scale Non Working Lights (5)
1:12 Scale Dollhouse Candle Sticks & Candles (3)
1:12 Scale Oil Lamps (1)
1:12 Scale Table Lamps (1)
Dolls House Wood Turned Miniatures (3)
1:12 DIY Kits (1)
Jewellery Findings And Beads (279)
Jewellery Beads (79)
Crystal Bicone Beads (12)
Crystal Facet and Roundelle Beads (15)
Glass Beads (5)
Metal Beads (20)
Pearl Beads (3)
Other Beads (10)
Jewellery Filigrees (6)
Jewellery Findings (142)
Bead Caps (18)
Cameos & Rhinestones (8)
Clasps & Fittings (22)
Frames (2)
Miscellaneous Jewellery Components (61)
Settings (31)
Micro Jewellery Findings (52)
Sale Items (15)
Top
